[{"answer": " You ready to shoot some hoops", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 13, "question": "", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Yeah, I guess.  I dont really feel like playing today", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 14, "question": " You ready to shoot some hoops", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Whats up?  You sick or something", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Yeah, I guess.  I dont really feel like playing today", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " No, nothing like that.  I just got the results of my GRE test, thats all", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Whats up?  You sick or something", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Howd you do", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 17, "question": " No, nothing like that.  I just got the results of my GRE test, thats all", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Not great", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Howd you do", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " Did you get a high enough score to apply to that school you wanted to go to ou", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 19, "question": " Not great", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " University of California.  I did, but barely", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 23, "question": " Did you get a high enough score to apply to that school you wanted to go to ou", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " Well than, what are you worrying about?  As long as you got a high enough scor", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 24, "question": " University of California.  I did, but barely", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " The GRE score is a big deal.  There are hundreds of people applying, and all o", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 31, "question": " Well than, what are you worrying about?  As long as you got a high enough scor", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " Well, what was the GRE requirement", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 35, "question": " The GRE score is a big deal.  There are hundreds of people applying, and all o", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " 1000", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Well, what was the GRE requirement", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " What did you get", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 37, "question": " 1000", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " 1010", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 38, "question": " What did you get", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " Thats good enough.  I wouldnt get all worked up about it though", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 39, "question": " 1010", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " Really", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 40, "question": " Thats good enough.  I wouldnt get all worked up about it though", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " No.  I mean the GRE score is just one small part of the application", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 41, "question": " Really", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " I guess", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 42, "question": " No.  I mean the GRE score is just one small part of the application", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " Schools dont just look at that only.  They look at the whole package", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 43, "question": " I guess", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " I did get two really great recommendation letters.  One was from my departmen", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 44, "question": " Schools dont just look at that only.  They look at the whole package", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " Thats awesome.  See?  Howd you get the one from the president", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 48, "question": " I did get two really great recommendation letters.  One was from my departmen", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " I was a student worker in his office and did some jobs for him, so he wrote m", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 49, "question": " Thats awesome.  See?  Howd you get the one from the president", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " Well, thats going to look impressive", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 51, "question": " I was a student worker in his office and did some jobs for him, so he wrote m", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " Hopefully", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 52, "question": " Well, thats going to look impressive", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " And you have all the other things going for you that make you better than othe", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Hopefully", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " I dont know about that.  Like what", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 59, "question": " And you have all the other things going for you that make you better than othe", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " Like all the stuff you do at school, for one.  Youre assistant coach of the basketbal", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 60, "question": " I dont know about that.  Like what", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " Do you think that matters", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 64, "question": " Like all the stuff you do at school, for one.  Youre assistant coach of the basketbal", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Of course.  That looks really good in an application.  Not many other people do a", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 68, "question": " Do you think that matters", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " Maybe", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 72, "question": " Of course.  That looks really good in an application.  Not many other people do a", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " And what about your grades.  You have a 4.0 and you won that award for writing", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 73, "question": " Maybe", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " I won the national award for journalistic excellence", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 77, "question": " And what about your grades.  You have a 4.0 and you won that award for writing", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " There you go.  Thats going to catch the eye of the Admissions Offices", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 78, "question": " I won the national award for journalistic excellence", "qSentId": 77},{"answer": " I guess youre right.  Maybe I shouldnt worry so much about the test score", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 79, "question": " There you go.  Thats going to catch the eye of the Admissions Offices", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " Its just a test score.  All the other parts of the application really show who you ar", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 80, "question": " I guess youre right.  Maybe I shouldnt worry so much about the test score", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " Thanks, Bill.  I feel a lot better", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 84, "question": " Its just a test score.  All the other parts of the application really show who you ar", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " No problem.  Now, are you ready to play some ball", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 85, "question": " Thanks, Bill.  I feel a lot better", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " Lets do it", "docId": "06-01", "aSentId": 86, "question": " No problem.  Now, are you ready to play some ball", "qSentId": 85}]
